(♪♪♪)
(SCREAMS)
SARAH:
Honey.
Honey, wake up.
Wake up.
I'm here.
You're okay.
You were dreaming.
It got me. It got me.
(CRYING)
SARAH:
Oh, baby.
Baby, it's okay.
You were sleepwalking again.
Oh, you're all right, honey.
Baby, calm down.
You're okay.
Mm.
Careful, it's hot.
You want marshmallows?
No?
You feelin'
a little bit better?
Mom, does everyone sleepwalk?
No, not everyone.
Some people.
I stopped when I was
about your age.
How did you make
the nightmares go away?
Well, you remember
the trick I taught you?
You look down at your hand
and you count your fingers.
You can't count
when you're dreaming,
you'll never get to five.
That's when I'd know
I was asleep
and I'd wake myself up.
What are you doing?
Just making sure.
Mm-hmm.
Mom, can I sleep
with you tonight?
What?
(CHUCKLES)
How can I say no
to that face?
(CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS)
Mom?
Yeah?
How do we know
we're not dreaming right now?
'Cause we're awake,
we're having
a normal conversation,
and we're gonna go
to sleep,
and we'll wake up again
in six hours, hopefully.
But when I wake up,
sometimes I'm still dreaming.
Mm.
Get some sleep, baby.
We gotta get up early.
Love you, Mom.
Love you, too.
So much.
(♪♪♪)
Aimee?
Where are you?
Answer me, please.
Hello?
AIMEE:
6, 10, 3, 5, 2, 7, 14, 9--
SARAH:
Hey, sweetheart.
You okay?
AIMEE:
5, 2, 6, 11, 4--
SARAH:
Wake up, baby.
AIMEE:
6, 10, 3, 5, 2, 7--
Hey, you're sleepwalking again.
AIMEE:
No, you are.
(GASPING)
(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
(♪♪♪)
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
You're not gonna
bring her back
by staring into the void,
you know?
God, Mom,
you scared me.
Jumpy?
Bad dreams again?
(SIGHS)
So real this time.
She was alive.
I held her
in my arms.
You were sleepwalking again,
weren't you?
Yeah.
GLORIA:
You have to start locking
your bedroom door at night.
Do you know how many people
fall to their deaths each year
from sleepwalking
out of windows,
down the stairs?
It's a fact.
I read it on the internet.
Sarah, hon, have you thought
about going back
to that support group?
I told you it didn't do
anything for me.
It was an accident.
A horrible, terrible accident,
but it wasn't your fault.
Sometimes the universe
just allows things to happen--
I don't wanna hear
that the universe allows
or doesn't allow bullshit.
I am tired of it.
I've heard it all my life.
(♪♪♪)
(SIGHS)
(GAME BEEPING)
Holden, we gotta go.
You're gonna be late
for school.
Grandma packed
your lunch, right?
Hello?
Can you at least text me
from that thing
if you're not gonna
talk to me?
Wow.
Okay.
You can stay here
and catch the bus.
(♪♪♪)
SARAH:
Put that down
for a second, please.
Listen, I know things
have been hard on you
after what happened.
New school,
new friends--
No friends, you mean.
SARAH:
That'll change, okay?
You have to try
to make friends.
Put in some effort.
Things will get better.
You'll see.
We're gonna move
back home?
You know we can't afford
to do that right now.
I don't mind living
with Grandma.
She's nice.
Yeah, well, not a fan.
That house gives me
bad dreams.
Oh, um, listen.
I have to drive into the city
this afternoon,
so Grandma's gonna pick you up
after school, okay?
Got it?
Um, bye?
Oh, I love you, too,
sweetheart!
(DOOR SHUTS)
SARAH:
I haven't sleep walked
since I was a kid.
But it was never like this.
Never.
Every single night.
It's out of control.
It only makes sense.
Look at everything
you went through.
All that trauma, for years.
And then your daughter.
I mean, you're haunted.
You're haunted
by her memory.
Oh, yeah.
It's overwhelming.
I wake up every single night
in a panic,
can't go back to sleep,
and then I'm walking around
the next day
like a damn zombie.
Hmm.
Well, you just need to channel
all of that into your art.
Pull it out of your psyche.
Let it free you.
I mean, it is the best form
of therapy.
You know this.
-I do.
-Yeah.
So, you wanna talk about
the new work?
I know.
It's gotten darker.
ANIYA:
I mean, I think it's great.
Really strong.
And you know me,
I'm not just saying that.
I think it's the start
of something new.
Mm, God, that's all I want,
the start of something new.
Listen, I wanna put your work
in next month's group show.
It'll draw a big crowd.
Cavanaugh will be featured.
Like, Lawrence Cavanaugh?
Mm-hmm.
-SARAH: What?
-Yeah.
Why not give him a solo show?
He only has a few new pieces,
but it'll be huge,
and it'll bring collectors
from all over New England.
And I think they'll love
your new work.
Oh, my God!
Aniya, thank you, thank you,
thank you!
Oh, that's amazing.
Oh, of course.
What are old friends for?
But I need you to finish up
the new pieces, okay?
-I will.
-No pressure.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
That's incredible.
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(DOOR SHUTS)
(GAME BEEPING)
Holden, look what I got.
Celebratory pizza.
It's your favorite,
extra cheese and pepperoni.
GLORIA:
Oh, all that cheese
binds me up.
You didn't put olives
on that thing, did you?
You know I hate olives.
No, Mom.
No olives.
Oh, geez, hon.
You're looking rough.
Your eyes have serious
baggage under--
Really?
Not even "Congratulations
on the show, Sara.
Happy for you."?
You need spiritual alignment.
You are all out of whack,
you know?
All pent up in here.
All the time.
Is it possible to eat
without getting a lecture
like I'm still
a hapless teenager?
Or is it just in your DNA
to give ridiculous advice?
Just trying to help.
I don't need advice, Mom.
I need sleep.
(EXHALES)
(PILLS RATTLING)
(♪♪♪)
(SIGHS)
(GIGGLING)
SARAH:
Oh, my gosh,
they have ponies.
It's your favorite!
Pretty.
-Look at that big one.
-Whoa.
(HOLDEN CHUCKLES)
Oh, look at the goats.
They got the weirdest eyes.
AIMEE:
Yeah.
Hey, can we get
some cotton candy?
Absolutely not.
That stuff is poison.
They can have a little bit.
They never have
that kind of stuff.
Here, baby,
I'll buy you some.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What did I just say?
Michael, let them be kids
for once.
Stop.
Holden, Holden, here.
Then you have to share it
with your sister though.
-Are you serious right now?
-I want to ride the horses!
Keep an eye on her.
Don't let her run off.
Aimee!
You sure you wanna wait?
It's a long line.
All right. All right.
AIMEE:
Oh, my gosh,
he's so pretty.
Look at his mane.
Aimee!
(SCREAMS)
Oh!
WRANGLER:
Whoa!
Aimee!
WRANGLER:
Calm down.
Oh, my God,
are you okay?
Don't ever do that again.
You can't run off like that.
MICHAEL:
What did I just say?
What did I just said?
I said keep an eye on her!
Look at what you did!
She's fine.
I didn't think she was gonna
take off like that.
I can't keep her chained
to my wrist.
But you could actually
watch her.
She could've got killed!
(SIGHS)
MICHAEL:
Are you incompetent?
Do you actually
fucking listen?
It's like you're purposely
fucking ignoring me!
Holden?
Aimee?
(GASPS)
(SOBS)
Sarah!
(PANTING)
(STROKING)
(♪♪♪)
(EXHALES)
(CAR WHIRRING)
♪ Think I might need you
more than I thought ♪
SARAH:
(INDISTINCT SPEECH)
You like the red?
AIMEE:
(INDISTINCT SPEECH)
SARAH:
Wow, look at that.
You like the red?
-Yes, I do.
-(LAUGHS)
Um, here.
Open this one, kiddo.
What is it?
I don't know.
You're gonna have
to open it.
Unless you wanna guess.
Hmm.
Feels like...
-It's a box of air.
-(LAUGHS)
-It's a hot air balloon.
(LAUGHING)
I love it!
-Aw!
-Oh.
I'm so glad.
-(AIMEE GIGGLES)
-Ah!
I'm gonna get the cake.
Got it. Yes.
(INDISCERNIBLE CHATTER)
Pew, pew, pew.
-All right. You ready, kiddo?
-Yes!
Okay.
Close your eyes.
No peeking.
(GIGGLES)
(TOGETHER)
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear, Aimee ♪
And many more.
(LAUGHING)
SARAH:
Make a wish.
Wooh!
I felt that.
It's gonna come true.
Time for cake!
Yay!
(GIGGLES)
MICHAEL:
I told you
this was important.
Do you think I wanna go?
I mean, you know how I feel
about public speaking.
You knew
I wouldn't be able to go.
But of course you have
to take Alyssa with you,
because she's indispensable,
right?
She's my assistant.
What the fuck's
your problem?
I mean, she's not even
remotely attractive!
God, you are disgusting.
Especially what you admitted
to doing
after I was pregnant
with Aimee.
Are you gonna bring that up
every fucking time?
It's like your
goddamn trump card.
Seriously,
I can't get around it.
Every fucking time!
Fuck!
I want a divorce.
A what?
Yeah?
Are you out
of your fucking mind?
I've been talking
to a lawyer.
-MICHAEL: Oh, yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
What firm?
You'll find out
soon enough.
It's over, Michael.
We're done.
Absolutely not!
You really wanna
break up this family?
What for?
Why would you wanna do that?
SARAH:
You know why.
The last couple bruises
you gave me,
I took pictures
and I've been recording
your outbursts, too.
The lies, the screaming,
the abuse, all of it!
Oh, you're recording it
right now, huh?
SARAH:
Mm-hmm.
You are such a gaslighter.
Constantly leading me
into fights
and confrontation
just so you can
leverage it all
by recording me.
It's not gonna work,
you know?
In fact, it'll actually have
the opposite effect in court.
I highly doubt the photos
of my bruises
will have the opposite effect
in court.
You did that to yourself.
What?
MICHAEL:
Yeah.
You are inhuman!
Fuck you,
you miserable fucking bitch!
(GASPS)
Oh, Michael, no!
No!
Delete.
-Delete!
-SARAH: No, you gotta stop!
Where is your
precious evidence now, huh?
Where's your grandmaster
fucking plan now?
You are not
gonna take my kids from me!
Calm down.
Stop.
Do you hear me?
Never! Ever!
(SARAH GASPING)
(PANTS)
(SNIFFLES)
(EXHALES)
(TAKES DEEP BREATHS)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
IN BACKGROUND)
(MACHINE BEEPING)
(♪♪♪)
Hi, Michael.
I wanted to come here
and say...
I'm sorry.
I wanted to forgive you
for everything you did.
I really wanted to.
But I can't.
You took her from me,
like you always said you would.
As much as I wished
that reality
could somehow start over,
play out differently...
it can't.
It won't.
She's gone,
because of you.
JOELLE:
What are you doing here?
Hey, Joelle.
Long time.
I just needed to come here
and say my peace.
Yeah, I heard what you said,
blaming him for everything.
You ruined
my brother's life.
You did this to him,
left him
when he needed you
the most.
He wouldn't
let me leave him.
He used every legal trick,
every connection
with the courts.
Please, the courts always take
the mom's side.
If you'd only let him
see his kids
like any dad
has a right to.
He had too many rights.
He was a monster.
He pushed me down
the goddamn stairs
and you know that!
Still sticking with that story?
Of course you are.
Because you couldn't
just push for a divorce,
you had to ruin his life,
didn't you?
Ruin his...
You know
what he did to me.
You were there for me,
you remember that?
At least you pretended
to be.
Don't twist this around.
Aimee wanted to be
with her father.
She always did.
Those kids meant
everything to him.
And you could've stayed
with him for them.
But no, you could
only think about yourself.
How dare you?
Do you have any idea
what this has done to me?
He needed you,
and you threw him away.
And now...
Now he might never wake up
because of you.
Let's just end it
right there, okay,
before I completely
lose my shit.
Because I'm about to.
I really am.
Goodbye, Joelle.
(SCOFFS)
Go to hell.
(♪♪♪)
They're my kids, too,
you fucking bitch.
Get out.
Fucking leave!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(AIMEE SCREAMS)
(♪♪♪)
Holden, you know my rule
about cellphones at the table.
Sorry, Grandma.
You can watch your boobtube
after dinner.
YouTube.
Whatever.
So how was everyone's day?
Hmm?
Anything interesting happen?
Well, I watched
a fascinating documentary
about the futility
of human existence.
Jesus, Mom.
Well, you know,
I really don't have
much to do
except think all day,
and I realized that we are all
just talking animals,
constantly trying
to distract ourselves
from the truth
of our human purpose.
Holden, you were put
on this Earth as a pure spirit.
You did a great job
with the tuna casserole.
Well, thank you.
What?
You don't like your dinner?
Answer Grandma, please.
I was with Dad last night.
(♪♪♪)
With Dad?
In my dreams.
What happened?
He tried
to take me away again.
I didn't wanna go.
(KNOCKING THE DOOR)
Holden,
come on out, buddy.
It was a nightmare, Holden.
It felt so real.
You remember
the counting trick, right?
Next time you have a nightmare,
you count your fingers.
Okay?
Can I be excused?
Yeah.
They're coming
to get you, Barbara.
Stop it!
You're ignorant!
Holden?
JOHNNY: (ON TV)
They're coming
for you, Barbara.
BARBARA: (ON TV)
Stop it!
You're acting like a child.
JOHNNY: (ON TV)
They're coming for you.
Baby.
BARBARA: (ON TV)
No! No!
SARAH:
Yeah, wake up.
Get you to bed.
Let's get those teeth brushed,
it's getting late.
(♪♪♪)
I'm awake now.
Well, it's past 10:00 p.m.,
you gotta get some sleep.
Can I at least be on my tablet
for a few more minutes, please?
No.
You know the rule.
Your devices stay downstairs
at night.
No bargaining.
It's just
I don't really wanna go
to sleep right now.
Well, just close your eyes
and think beautiful things,
like the beach,
camping in the woods.
The petting zoo?
Why'd you bring that up?
I was just dreaming about it.
The horse
that scared Aimee.
Dad was so mad at you.
That's not
a nice memory, Holden.
Think about Disney World.
Hmm?
You remember
Space Mountain?
You threw up that gummy candy
all over me.
Disney World was the best.
Yeah.
Think good thoughts.
Happy thoughts.
Good night.
(♪♪♪)
SARAH:
Hello?
(♪♪♪)
(GASPING)
Sarah, I miss you so much.
(PANTING)
SARAH:
This is a dream.
(PANTING)
I have to wake up.
HOLDEN:
Mom!
(GASPS)
Oh, God!
Holden.
Oh! Thank you, baby.
If it weren't for you...
Oh, my God,
you saved me.
Mom, why do you sleepwalk
so much?
I don't know.
No one knows.
I think something's wrong,
but I'm gonna find out.
Okay?
I'm gonna get help.
Baby.
(EXHALES)
I've had multiple
near misses now.
I could have killed myself.
I have no control
over my body while I'm asleep,
and that is terrifying.
What's going on?
Am-- am I crazy?
Is my subconscious
trying to kill me?
Or...
You mentioned
taking medication.
What were you prescribed?
Um, I...
No, I...
I sometimes take
my mother's sleeping pills
once in a while,
not often,
hoping that they'll
knock me out hard enough
that I won't sleepwalk.
That's not advisable, Sarah.
Barely helps anyway.
I think your nightmares
and sleepwalking
are a manifestation
of misplaced guilt.
You didn't cause
that accident.
You invited your husband over
for closure, that's it.
Did I?
I want us-- I want us
to be a family again,
like we're supposed to be.
That's not gonna happen.
I don't think so.
You wanna know something
really disturbing?
I can handle
the nightmares,
as long as I get to see Aimee...
even if it's just for a second.
That's fucked up, right?
It's clearly not normal.
Well, nightmares
aren't normal, no.
Yeah, but it's the sleepwalking
that scares me.
I just need something
that is going to shut it down.
I'm not aware of any medication
that can do that safely.
But I'm gonna refer you
to a specialist.
They'll do some tests.
This could be
neurophysiological
for all we know.
We're gonna
figure this out, okay?
We got this.
Beloved
and compassionate spirits,
assist me in releasing
all energies and intrusions
that are not
in divine alignment.
Hello?
What are you doing?
Did you drop acid or are you
just trying to freak me out?
I am calling
on our ancestors
to get rid of all this
bad energy in the house.
It's like cobwebs.
It's giving me a headache.
Right.
Well, I hope it helps.
GLORIA:
This is coming
from your mind, you know?
You're bringing it in.
It's a spiritual force.
Um, Mom, you do know
that the '70s ended
a long time ago, right?
(BLOWS AIR)
But if you do have
any sweet drugs stashed away
that you'd like to share...
Oh, God, I wish.
Beloved
and compassionate spirits,
assist me.
(KNOCK ON THE WINDOW)
AIMEE:
Holden.
Am I dreaming?
We're always dreaming,
even when we're awake.
Where have you been?
I missed you so much.
I've been waiting for you.
Come on.
Come outside and play.
(♪♪♪)
Oh, my God!
Holden!
Wake up!
Oh, my God!
Holden!
Baby!
Baby, wake up!
No! Holden!
No!
Baby, Holden!
No! No!
Oh, my God, Holden!
Oh, God.
Holden!
(CAR WHIRRING)
SARAH:
Baby! Stop!
Oh, my God, stop!
(CAR HONKING)
Oh, my God!
You're okay.
You're okay, honey.
I was with Aimee.
I saw her.
Oh, sweetie,
you were sleepwalking.
Baby, you were sleepwalking.
You're all right.
Oh, my God.
Oh, okay.
What the hell
are you two doing?
Get inside before
you freeze your asses off.
Come on.
(LIGHT FLICKERING)
Damn wiring.
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
We'll make sure the windows
can't be opened at night,
and we're gonna lock
our doors, too.
You know, you shouldn't wake
a sleepwalker.
It's dangerous.
(SCOFFS)
That's an old wives' tale.
GLORIA:
No, it's true.
Just like if you die
in your sleep,
you get trapped
in your dream.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm sorry,
where did you read that?
That is some new age
hippie bullshit.
Excuse me.
I don't wanna
sleepwalk anymore.
You won't.
We'll make sure none of us
can leave our rooms at night,
okay?
We keep them locked.
Dad's back.
What?
Aimee, too.
They're both spirits.
You were dreaming, Holden.
His ghost talks to me
through the door.
"Come with me, Holden.
Come with me."
Maybe that was
just a memory.
That happened
before the accident, remember?
Shh.
Listen.
Can you hear them?
They're close.
Who is?
Aimee?
Help me.
Please.
(SCREAMING)
Oh, my God.
Am I still dreaming?
(EXHALES)
So then how did you sleepwalk
through a locked door?
I don't know.
I must have walked in
and pulled it shut.
Okay.
I guess that's possible.
Just freaking weird.
HOLDEN:
I had a dream last night.
I was with Aimee.
We were playing outside
like we used to.
You were with Aimee?
I thought I was dreaming
for hours,
but when I woke up,
it was only a few minutes.
Well, that's how dreams work.
You know, it can be hours
or even days,
but it's really just
a few minutes.
You know, I had a dream
not long ago
that I was
back in high school,
and a whole year went by.
Football games,
prom,
and then suddenly
I'm at graduation
and completely stark naked,
you know?
(MIMICS A SOUND)
I mean, like everything,
everything just out there.
Huh, it was mortifying.
Why do I even bother?
That was
way too much information.
(GAME BEEPING)
(WATER RUNNING)
Can you
turn that down, please?
Or go play somewhere else?
I swear to God you're turning
into a goddamn zombie.
(SIGHS)
Holden, I didn't mean that.
I'm sorry!
So listen, I invited my friend
Bai over tomorrow night
to do a cleansing.
Who?
Bai.
Bai Zhou.
She's Buddhist.
Oh, come on,
you remember her, don't you?
She used to do
my Tarot card readings
when you were a kid.
You have had some weird friends
over the years.
Thanks.
SARAH:
What kind of cleansing
is this anyway?
Please don't tell me
it's an exorcism.
Technically it's an exorcism,
but she's good.
She just cleansed a house
last summer in Danville.
Well, can she get rid
of Michael,
but Aimee gets to stay?
I don't think it works
that way.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Yeah.
Cerebral atrophy?
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
I retain the right.
We're technically still married
even though I...
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
I'll be in later today.
Thank you.
Well, all I can say is
thank God that horrible man
is nearly off the planet.
He refused to give up the ghost
for way too long.
Mom, can you, like, just stop
and let me think about this?
Think about what?
Pull the goddamn plug.
Are you through?
Holden should see his father
one last time.
And I want you
to come with us.
Oh, Jesus H. Christ
on a crutch.
I'll get my coat.
I'll get him ready.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
SARAH:
Hi.
Oh, hi.
Are you Mrs. Anders?
I go by Pangborn now.
We were separated
before the accident.
Understood.
I'm Dr. Henson.
We spoke on the phone.
I'm new here.
Uh, this is kind
of embarrassing,
but I think I was wrong
about the cerebral atrophy.
Wrong?
How so?
Well, he's on
a definite decline,
that's for sure,
but he does have occasional
intermittent increases
in brain activity.
Increases?
I'm sorry,
I don't understand.
Well, I went through his files
and it's been happening
since the accident.
Every night
during REM sleep,
sudden intense bursts
of gamma waves.
It's really extraordinary
in a comatose patient.
I've never seen
anything like it.
So what does that mean?
Well, sleep and dreams
are still the Wild West
of consciousness research.
But high gamma like that,
that usually means
lucid dreaming.
Taking control
of his dreams.
(GASP)
-Oh!
-Oh, God.
Oh, it happens.
It's involuntary.
It can be
a little unsettling.
A little?
I almost pissed myself.
Holden.
Hey!
(CRYING)
Holden.
Hey.
Hey, honey.
Oh.
Come here.
It's okay.
I know it's hard.
Let it out.
JOELLE:
Sarah?
Can I speak with you
for a moment?
Just us.
Holden, love,
go with Grandma, please.
GLORIA:
Come on, kiddo.
Let's get some candy.
Any kind you want.
I just...
I wanted to apologize
for the other day.
I said...
What I said was cruel
and heartless, and I'm sorry.
I've just been under a lot
of pressure lately.
I'm barely sleeping, and--
and I'm...
SARAH:
It's okay.
I mean, we're all
going through this.
I've been having nightmares,
really frightening ones.
Like Michael's trying
to reach out to me,
tell me something.
Or maybe I'm just trying
to deal
with all of this
subconsciously.
I don't know, but I feel like
I'm losing my mind,
like reality is slipping away
in increments.
Believe me, I know.
I've been spiraling every day
since the accident.
I had a dream
where he tried to warn me.
I think he was trying
to tell me about you.
What?
So, what are you planning
on doing with Michael?
'Cause I know you've been
talking to the doctors.
(SIGHS)
Well, it's been nearly
three months.
He's not getting any better.
Just please,
maybe let him
hang on a little bit longer.
Please.
I have a feeling
he's gonna wake up very soon.
Look, I know it.
He tells me he is.
Look, I-- I know
this has been hell.
And I know you blame me.
No, not anymore.
Look, everyone knows
Michael had issues.
He was cruel
when we were kids.
Picked on me all the time.
But he was my brother.
He's my brother.
I'm so sorry, Joelle.
If I could change things,
turn back time.
I know.
Believe me, I know.
Is Holden in his room?
Yeah, I told him to stay there
until the insanity was over.
I can't believe I let you
talk me into a séance.
I don't know
what I was thinking.
This is good for your soul.
A releasing
of the unconscious forces.
It's exactly what you need.
God, let's just get
this over with, please.
Oh!
(CONTINUOUS BELL RINGING
AND KNOCKING ON THE DOOR)
Bai Zhou!
Aw, it's been too long.
Hey!
How you doin', girl?
Oh, how long has it been?
Oh, you lookin' old.
Your wrinkles got wrinkles!
Well, when you were a kid,
the rainbows
were in black
and white.
(LAUGHS)
-SARAH: Hi.
-Oh, wow!
Last time I saw you,
you were in college.
You're getting old, too.
It's good to see you, too, Bai.
(BAI LAUGHS)
Oh, there's a darkness
around you.
Not inside, but out.
It's like a great big shadow
over you.
GLORIA:
Sara's been having
really bad dreams.
She's sleepwalking.
We need you
to put an end to it.
Yes.
Ah, yes.
I sense presences here,
all around you.
Are you saying the house
is haunted?
No, houses aren't haunted,
people, people are haunted.
Ghosts latch onto you
most of the time.
We never see them,
but they can affect your health.
That's why
they used to say
a person's in low spirits
or high spirits.
Ghosts come
out of the mind,
but that doesn't make them
any less real.
Well, that is,
uh, comforting.
So, let's get
the party started.
Uh, you got anything to drink,
like a whiskey sour?
(♪♪♪)
Okay, I want you
to understand this
from a different perspective,
a Buddhist perspective.
Reality is a construct
of the brain.
It's full
of supernatural beings.
They can all be invited in
through the mind.
Sometimes willingly,
sometimes not.
What about if someone's
barely holding onto life?
Can they manifest
into nightmares?
Of course.
The soul is not always tethered
to the body.
It's free to roam around
at night while we dream.
The Chinese used to believe
that sleepwalkers
were possessed
by evil spirits.
The demon would try
and lead them to their death.
They'd take them to the forest
or a lake to drown,
or even sleepwalk them
straight off a cliff.
Uh, what are the pen
and paper for?
I'm gonna see
if I can summon the spirits
into ink, and try and find out
how to put them to rest.
(CHANTS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
He's close.
He's getting closer
every day.
He's not dead. No.
Not yet.
You told her about Michael.
I swear I didn't say a word.
Oh, he's cruel, monstrous,
and angry!
So angry.
He feels wronged by you.
He wants his son back.
(CHANTING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
He wants to be
with you again.
He wants to reunite
on the other side,
the place where death
and dreams meet.
He's getting closer.
He's drawing near.
(SCRIBBLING)
(LIGHTS FLICKERING)
What the hell is this?
Make it stop!
(PANTS)
This is happening.
This is real.
GLORIA:
Why are you here, Aimee?
(TOGETHER)
It's all one,
one endless dream.
He's coming for you.
He's almost here.
(SCREAMS)
Aimee?
Out! Be gone, spirit!
(PANTS)
(♪♪♪)
GLORIA:
Bai.
BAI: (IN MICHAEL'S VOICE)
Sarah, you're coming with me.
You and Holden, forever.
Leave my son alone!
(SCREAMS)
GLORIA:
No!
(GROANS)
Oh, God.
What's...
What's happening?
What--
(GROANS)
Bai.
No, Bai, don't.
Sarah, call 911.
OFFICER 1:
Did she have
any prior health issues
before today?
No, no, no.
She, um, she had
a history of seizures.
And, uh, she had a stroke
eight or nine years ago.
And, um, we were just having
a quiet evening.
I mean...
Oh, God.
Poor woman, you know?
We...
There-- there was really nothing
we could do.
She was just there,
and then...
(INDISCERNIBLE SPEECH)
(♪♪♪)
Hey, baby.
What's going on?
Nothing.
You excited for the show?
Yeah.
Really excited.
Hopefully sell
a few pieces,
then we can get
a place of our own.
So keep your fingers crossed.
Okay?
HOLDEN:
That looks like the ghost
from my dream.
Like Dad.
Yeah, except Dad
is still alive,
and ghosts can't be both
alive and dead
at the same time,
now can they?
Then why does he tell me
he's in hell?
Because they're just
bad dreams, hon.
That's it.
We're letting them get to us
way too much.
We gotta stay strong,
or the world will beat us down.
(♪♪♪)
(INDISCERNIBLE CHATTER
IN BACKGROUND)
GRETA:
Sarah, I think these new pieces
are an absolute revelation.
The shadow forms,
the chiaroscuro.
There's violence
under the surface.
Who are some
of your influences?
Um, you know,
I really like Giacometti--
It reminds me
of Marinella's work.
-Mm.
-Yeah, it's so fascinating.
Do you also know Chet Zar?
I mean, that is also
a very interesting artist.
-I love Chet Zar.
-Yeah, absolutely.
-I'm not familiar with his--
-Oh, look.
The belle of the ball
finally arrives.
AMIT:
Wow.
Cavanaugh made it
to his own show.
-SARAH: Thank you.
-That's a first.
GRETA:
Yes.
-ANIYA: Excuse me.
-Hi.
ANIYA:
Excuse me.
Sarah!
How's it going, girl?
Closing it up?
I'm trying to.
I'm exhausted.
Any interested buyers?
No, not yet,
but the night is still young.
Oh, hey.
There's Cavanaugh.
You want me to introduce you?
Mm, no.
No, it's--
Come on.
Stop being
so anti-social.
-You've got to meet him.
-I'm not.
Let's go.
Lawrence!
-Excuse me.
-ANIYA: Lawrence.
-Hi. (KISSING)
-Hi.
I want you to meet
Sarah Pangborn.
Oh.
You're Sarah Pangborn.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Possibly.
I have to say
I love your new work.
I am truly glad
you're a part of this show.
You are?
I'm-- I'm sorry.
I meant to say thank you.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You know, your style
is reminiscent of Francis Bacon.
It's so stark
and emotionally raw.
That's a huge compliment.
I've never even considered
my work in the same realm.
Well, I think it's a direction
you should continue to explore.
Do you know
James Jarenson?
SARAH:
Yes.
Amazing artist.
Well, Jarenson
and Deidre Clem
were my mentors in New York
back in the '80s.
SARAH:
Will you excuse me
for a moment?
Yes, of course.
Everything okay?
SARAH:
I'll be right back.
Aimee?
Baby, turn around, please.
Please?
Oh, God.
(GASPS)
Hello?
Aimee?
Sarah.
Come with me.
Forever.
No.
Where's Aimee?
Give her to me!
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING, SOBBING)
Sarah!
(INDISCERNIBLE CHATTER)
(CRYING)
(PILLS RATTLING)
(♪♪♪)
(PANTING)
(EXHALES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING IN DISTANCE)
(DRINK POURING)
(SIGHS)
(PHONE RINGING)
Hey, Joelle.
Hey, I'm just
calling you back.
SARAH: (ON PHONE)
It's been almost a week.
The doctors say he's still
on a steady decline.
He's just...
He's not improving.
JOELLE: (ON PHONE)
I know.
He's getting worse.
He wants it to end.
I can feel it.
It's like he's reaching out
to me.
We all wanna hold on
for a miracle, but...
JOELLE: (ON PHONE)
No.
No, he's suffered long enough.
It's time.
Okay.
Uh, I will call you tomorrow
and we'll make the arrangements.
Take care, Joelle.
When Michael dies,
he's not gonna let you go.
Why would you say that?
You were there.
You heard what came out
of Bai's mouth.
That man is in a coma.
He's not even dead yet,
but his spirit got through.
But...
Uh, you said it yourself,
Mom,
I-- I need to let them go.
They're just projections.
No.
We saw them.
They're real.
Mother, please!
Please, this is...
God, this is making me
feel sick.
I can't handle it.
Hear me out.
What if Michael's spirit
gets stronger
once it's free
from his body?
What then?
How are you
gonna protect yourself?
gonna protect your son?
Stop!
I don't wanna keep talking
about this anymore.
It's making me crazy.
Okay, fine!
Don't listen to me.
Just...
Forget everything
I just said.
I need to get out.
I need to be out
of this house for a while.
Make sure Holden's in bed
by 9:00.
Please.
(♪♪♪)
MICHAEL:
Just give me
one more chance, please.
That's all I ask,
just one more chance.
I gave you
too many chances.
You need help, Michael,
serious psychiatric help.
Stop saying that!
(♪♪♪)
(RINGING)
ANIYA: (ON PHONE)
Hey, Sarah.
How are you?
Hey.
I was just out
for a drive.
Wondering if you wanna grab
a drink.
Or three.
ANIYA: (ON PHONE)
Are you feeling all right?
I just need a night out
and some good company.
ANIYA: (ON PHONE)
Well, Sarah, honestly,
I don't think
you should be driving
a car while you're sleeping.
What?
(♪♪♪)
(GASPS)
Oh, no!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING, GASPING)
(PANTING)
Jesus fucking Christ!
(CRYING)
(SIGHS)
Are you sure you don't need me
to come with you?
I know it's not
gonna be easy.
It's okay.
Just stay here and keep
Holden's mind off things.
This is something
I have to do alone.
It's gonna end after this.
No more nightmares.
No more sleepwalking, right?
Come here.
You got this.
You're very strong.
You get that from me.
I love you, kiddo.
Love you, too.
(♪♪♪)
(MACHINE BEEPING)
(MACHINE STATIC)
VOICEOVER ARTIST: (ON TV)
And you get all that for just
three easy payments of 9.95.
(PEOPLE CHEERING ON TV)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR SHUTS)
Hey, baby.
It's over.
Dad's gone?
Yeah.
But it's like we talked about.
He's no longer suffering.
No more bad dreams.
SARAH:
There you go,
snug as a bug.
Try to get some sleep.
Okay?
(KISSES)
I will never let anything
happen to you.
Ever.
I love you, Mom.
(KISSES)
I love you, too, so much.
(EXHALES)
(KETTLE BEEPING)
(DRINK POURING)
(GULPING)
(♪♪♪)
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
(THUD IN DISTANCE)
Mom?
(♪♪♪)
(THUDDING IN DISTANCE)
(EXHALES)
Holden!
This is your fault.
Aimee.
It's your fault I'm here.
Oh, God.
I am so sorry, Aimee.
I love you so much.
You're my love.
You wanna know
the truth?
I wanted to go
with him.
Don't say that.
Please.
HOLDEN:
Mom.
Mom!
Holden!
(HOLDEN SCREAMS)
Holden?
MICHAEL:
Sarah.
Sarah!
(GASPS)
Sarah.
Wake up!
Please. Wake up!
Please.
MICHAEL AND GLORIA: (TOGETHER)
Sarah, wake up!
(SCREAMS)
(THUDDING)
(CRYING)
Grandma?
It's okay.
It's all right.
It's not real.
Baby, it's not real.
Okay?
It's just a dream.
We're gonna wake up
and it's gonna be all better.
Okay? I promise.
We're gonna wake up.
(SIREN BEEPING)
No, she didn't have
any other health issues.
I think she was sleepwalking.
Sleepwalking?
That happened frequently?
Yeah, occasionally.
Runs in the family.
I do it.
Even my son sleepwalks.
I'm sorry, do you think
this is gonna take much longer?
(THUNDER IN DISTANCE)
SARAH:
I had to say those things
to protect you.
You know that?
You shoulda told them
the truth.
Your father is doing this.
You can't see it,
but it's him.
Grandma was right.
You need help.
He wants to take you
away from me.
I'll never let that happen,
do you hear me?
Never ever.
Yeah, that sounds doable.
And we don't need
a big funeral.
Um, most of her friends
have already passed away.
It'll just be
about a dozen of us.
Yeah.
Thank you.
(CRYING)
(SIMMERING)
(CHOPPING)
(SNIFFLES)
Sorry, dinner's a little late.
It's your favorite, curry.
(GRUNTS)
Dig in, guys.
It's getting cold.
(MUNCHING)
It's good.
Spicy.
Well, enjoy it.
This'll be the last time.
I don't want it
to be the last time.
I want you back.
I want my kids back.
Michael.
Please, just let me finish.
I want us to be a family again,
like we're supposed to be.
That's not gonna happen.
We're separated.
One way or another,
we're getting a divorce.
I don't care how long
you try and drag this out.
Give me
one more chance, please.
That's all I ask,
just one more chance.
I gave you
too many chances,
and every time you went back
to your old ways.
You need help, Michael,
serious psychiatric help.
Stop saying that!
I'm so tired of you
fucking saying that.
Kids, go upstairs
and find Grandma.
Take your dinners
with you.
Mom and Dad
need to talk.
Stop yelling.
I'm done with it!
Done with your abuse!
Abuse?
You and your
pathetic allegations.
My lawyers have photos
of the bruises, Michael.
-And the black eye.
-Hmm.
Everyone's gonna know
who you are now.
Everyone.
(DISHES CLATTER)
You're lucky
I was so kind, so caring.
I gave up everything,
everything for you
and those kids,
my entire existence,
and this is what you do to me?
Go to hell.
They're my kids, too,
you fucking bitch.
Get off me. Get out!
Get out right now
or I will call the police!
-Just--
-SARAH: That's it!
-MICHAEL: Stop.
-That's it. That is it.
-Stop.
-Sarah, just--
SARAH:
That's it.
I'm calling them.
You did this.
You brought this on yourself.
-Just stop.
-DISPATCHER: (ON PHONE) 911.
Hi, is this the police?
Stop.
SARAH:
This is Sarah Pangborn.
MICHAEL:
Okay. Please.
DISPATCHER: (ON PHONE)
Ma'am?
Hello?
Please.
DISPATCHER: (ON PHONE)
Are you still there?
Hello?
I'm going.
Then get out.
DISPATCHER: (ON PHONE)
Are you in danger?
Right now!
Fucking leave!
DISPATCHER: (ON PHONE)
...police.
Go!
DISPATCHER: (ON PHONE)
Ma'am, we do hear yelling.
Ma'am, are you okay?
Ma'am, what's going on?
Hello?
Yeah, I'm here.
DISPATCHER: (ON PHONE)
Ma'am, are you okay?
I'm okay.
DISPATCHER: (ON PHONE)
Do you need assistance
from the police?
No, I'm, uh, I'm fine.
I, uh, he just-- he-- he left.
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(CAR DOOR SHUTS)
(♪♪♪)
(WATER RUNNING)
Dad!
Shh.
I thought you left.
I couldn't leave
without saying goodbye.
You know, your mom
didn't let me tell you
about the present
that I have for you,
the reason why I came here
is 'cause she'd be jealous,
'cause she knows how much
you're gonna like it.
What is it?
I don't know.
Okay.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, my gosh!
A piebald?
A Welsh Cob,
just like you wanted.
I mean, perfect markings,
perfect mane.
So we'll go down
to the stables in the morning,
but if we don't leave now,
your mom's never
gonna let you have him.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
It's okay?
Well, I'm gonna be
honest, okay?
Mom doesn't want you to go.
But I feel like
we can make an exception
just this once, right?
Me, too.
All right, come on.
(KNOCK ON THE DOOR)
Holden,
come on out, buddy.
It's your daddy.
Holden, come on.
Me and your sister
and you are gonna go on a trip.
Holden, open the door now.
Open the door.
Can we see him tonight,
just to say hi?
No, love.
First thing in the morning.
Daddy's tired.
(♪♪♪)
Daddy!
I-- I-- I'm-- I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Daddy's just a little tired.
(KETTLE WHISTLING)
-Daddy!
-MICHAEL: I'm okay.
We'll be home soon.
Don't worry.
(YAWNS)
Daddy's a little tired.
(KETTLE WHISTLING)
(WATER RUNNING)
I think she put something
in my food.
Who did?
Um, your mom.
(SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(PANTING)
Mom.
Dad took Aimee.
What?
Aimee!
(PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMS)
GLORIA:
That's how dreams work.
(♪♪♪)
GLORIA:
It can seem like hours
or even days go by.
(SARAH CHOCKING)
(GASPING)
GLORIA:
But only a few minutes
have passed.
(♪♪♪)